ADAM ISOM

Experienced full-stack software engineer and co-creator of Haven, an open-source developer tool for small teams that abstracts away the complexity of secrets management. Proficient with Ruby, Rails, JavaScript, Node.js, React, Redux, Bash, SQL, and all things AWS.

EXPERIENCE

Co-Creator and Software Engineer

2020 - present

Haven (https://haven-secrets.github.io/) ☐

- Designed, prototyped, and built Haven Core backend, using Node.js and AWS
- Implemented secure secrets storage following encryption best practices, and with low latency and high availability, using AWS SDKs and Amazon DynamoDB
- Enabled team management features such as fine-grained access control, flagging and revocation, and access logs, using Amazon DynamoDB and AWS IAM
- Solved new-user credentials distribution problem, using AWS Lambda
- Solved master key distribution problem, using AWS KMS
- Enabled application secrets to be fetched, decrypted, injected, and redacted from logs at runtime, using Node.js child processes
- Automated setup and teardown of cloud infrastructure, using AWS CloudFormation
- Designed and built two frontends, a web UI and a CLI, using React and Node.js
- Collaborated daily with a fully remote team of engineers
- Authored technical case study: https://haven-secrets.github.io/case-study

Software Engineer

2019 - present

Self-Employed

- A helpdesk ticket tracking application built with Ruby on Rails, deployed on Heroku
- A web application that allows viewing and filtering of airline routes, built with React
- A kanban board application built with React, Redux, Ruby on Rails, and PostgreSQL

SKILLS

Backend Frontend Cloud Other Ruby & Rails JavaScript (ES5 & ES6+) AWS (Lambda, DynamoDB, Git & GitHub Node.js CloudFormation, KMS, IAM) Bash / command line React Python Redux DigitalOcean Agile SQL (PostgreSQL, T-SQL) HTML5 & CSS3 Heroku RESTful APIs *jQuery*

EDUCATION

Western Governors University

2018 - present

B.S. Computer Science (103/122 credits completed)

University of Utah 2009 – 2015

B.S. Psychology